<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Daniel Moore</title>
    <link>https://danielmoore.work/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Daniel Moore</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 22:23:44 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://danielmoore.work/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Theres Something</title>
      <link>https://danielmoore.work/projects/theres-something/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 22:23:44 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielmoore.work/projects/theres-something/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>An Unsettled Supper</title>
      <link>https://danielmoore.work/projects/an-unsettled-supper/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 22:21:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielmoore.work/projects/an-unsettled-supper/</guid>
      <description>An Unsettled Supper.                           An Unsettled Supper is an experiment with collaborator Nicholas Tran, exploring how we could use the live-ness and intimacy offered by theatre in a black box space to amplify the experience of live horror. The show allowed only twelve audience members in each showing, and contained no dialogue, so we could really focus on creating an atmosphere of tension and fear using visual language, smell, and taste.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>rEMOTION</title>
      <link>https://danielmoore.work/projects/remotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 22:21:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielmoore.work/projects/remotion/</guid>
      <description>rEMOTION Play Festival.           rEMTION play festival was a socially-distanced open-admission play festival performed over Zoom and streamed live over Twitch. I directed three shows, one written for the stage and adapted to the medium, and two written specifically for the live-stream medium.  rEMOTION premiered in June, 2020.  Cast: The Exhibit  Cindy Giang Sarah Kaino Shelby Cox Sam Eglowitz   Live Now  Alice Zhang Nicholas Leung Chae Moon Kristina Jin   Sara  Kiana Triana Tabitha (Taii) Mehl Caryl Illana Alexa Passante     Creative Team: Writers  Hanna Wagner (The Exhibit) Nicholas Tran (Live Now) Sam Eglowitz (Sara)   Producers  Amy Côté(The Exhibit) Angela Zhao (Live Now) Irinola Megrelishvili (Sara)   Sound Designer: Eric Chen    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>untitled [redacted]</title>
      <link>https://danielmoore.work/projects/untitled-redacted/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 16 Oct 2020 22:21:37 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://danielmoore.work/projects/untitled-redacted/</guid>
      <description>untitled [redacted].     untitled [redacted] is an experiment in horror podcasting, applying what we&#39;ve learned from our theatre work into a related but unique field. A surreal ghost story spanning generations.  untitled [redacted] will debut late October, 2020, and continue through its run until late November, available anywhere you can find podcasts.  Cast: Chae Moon Kenny Yang Shelby Cox Sam Eglowitz Kristina Jin Angela Yang M.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
